Journal editors decide what gets published and what doesn’t, affecting the careers of other academics and influencing the direction that a field takes.
期刊编辑决定什么能发表、什么不能发表，既影响着其他学者的职业生涯，也影响着一个领域的发展方向。
You’d hope, then, that journals would do everything they can to establish a diverse editorial board, reflecting a variety of voices, experiences, and identities.
那么，人们会希望期刊竭尽所能，组建一个多元化的编委会，以体现多种多样的声音、经历和身份。
Unfortunately a new study in Nature Neuroscience makes for disheartening reading.
遗憾的是，《自然·神经科学》上的一项新研究读来令人沮丧。
The team finds that the majority of editors in top psychology and neuroscience journals are male and based in the United States: a situation that may be amplifying existing gender inequalities in the field and influencing the kind of research that gets published.
研究团队发现，顶级心理学和神经科学期刊的编辑大多是在美国工作的男性；这种状况可能正在加剧该领域现有的性别不平等，并影响着哪类研究能够发表。
Men were found to account for 60% of the editors of psychology journals.
研究发现，男性占心理学期刊编辑的60%。
There were significantly more male than female editors at each level of seniority, and men made up the majority of editors in over three quarters of the journals.
在每个资历级别上，男性编辑都显著多于女性编辑；在超过四分之三的期刊中，男性编辑占多数。
Crucially, the proportion of female editors was significantly lower than the overall proportion of women psychology researchers.
关键的是，女性编辑的比例显著低于心理学研究人员中女性的总体比例。
The differences were even starker in the neuroscience journals: 70% of editors were male, and men held the majority of editorial positions in 88% of journals.
神经科学期刊中的差异甚至更为悬殊：70%的编辑是男性，在88%的期刊中，男性占据了大多数编辑职位。
In this case, the proportion of female editors was not significantly lower than the proportion of female researchers working in neuroscience—a finding that reveals enduring gender disparities in the field more broadly.
就神经科学而言，女性编辑的比例并不显著低于该领域女性研究人员的比例——这一发现揭示出，从更大范围来看，该领域长期存在性别差距。
On the basis of their results, the team concludes that “the ideas, values and decision-making biases of men are overrepresented in the editorial positions of the most recognized academic journals in psychology and neuroscience.”
根据研究结果，该团队得出结论：“在心理学和神经科学领域最受认可的学术期刊中，男性的观点、价值观和决策偏见在编辑职位上占比过高。”
Gender inequality in science is often attributed to the fact that senior academics are more likely to be male, because historically science was male-dominated: it’s argued that as time goes on and more women rise to senior roles, the field will become more equal.
人们常把科学界的性别不平等归因于这一事实：科学在历史上由男性主导，因此资深学者更可能是男性；有观点认为，随着时间推移、越来越多的女性升任高级职位，这一领域将变得更加平等。
Yet this study showed that even the junior roles in psychology journals tended to be held disproportionately by men, despite the fact that there are actually more female than male junior psychology faculty.
然而，这项研究表明，即便是心理学期刊中的初级职位，也往往不成比例地由男性担任，尽管实际上心理学初级教员中女性比男性还多。
This implies that a lack of female academics is not the problem.
这意味着，问题并不在于缺少女性学者。
Instead, there are structural reasons that women are disadvantaged in science.
女性在科学界处于不利地位，背后另有结构性原因。
Women receive lower salaries and face greater childcare demands, for instance, which can result in fewer publications and grants—the kinds of things that journals look for when deciding who to appoint.
例如，女性拿的薪水更低，面临的育儿负担也更重，这可能导致她们发表的论文更少、获得的科研经费也更少——而这些都是期刊在决定任命谁时会看重的东西。
Rather than simply blaming the inequality of editorial boards on tradition, we should be actively breaking down these existing barriers.
我们不应只是把编委会中的不平等归咎于传统，而应积极破除这些现有的障碍。
A lack of diversity among journal editors also likely contributes to psychology’s WEIRD problem.
期刊编辑缺乏多样性，也很可能助长了心理学的WEIRD问题。
If journal editors are largely men from the United States, then they will probably place higher value on papers that are relevant to Western, male populations, whether consciously or not.
如果期刊编辑大多是来自美国的男性，那么无论有意还是无意，他们都很可能会更看重与西方男性人群相关的论文。